Look, you joined the company. How long did it
take before you took it over
with your brother?
A father, let's say, in his work as an
entrepreneur was very focused on
knowing about his work.  In those years,
however, fashion was changing.  He was a
great specialist in fabrics
[music]
cotur because in those years Ungaro,
Dior, Valentino, there was a whole
clothing system that wanted certain types
of materials.  In those years, however,
a certain [music] Mr. Armani appears
who gives an incredible shake-up to fashion
.  So from a system of
making clothes that was structured,
[music]
Giorgio Armani empties, eh empties the garment
of the ball, [music] deconstructs it
and has an incredible success and therefore
there is a need for a new generation of
materials, even different colors.
of the company was a sailing ship with sails
that had no wind and we were
also losing the wind of Armani who instead
had changed fashion because dad didn't
have that textile culture there, instead
at that moment it was my culture.
I came from a
completely different cultural experience, but I had lived there,
I had the cultural equipment and the
scent of my time and so I quickly began
to clash with my
father.  Ah.